{"instructions": ["This section is an extended version of the previous task, which is clicking on <strong>left to right</strong> or <strong>right to left</strong> to indicate the moving direction of the sound beep. <p></p>In cases where you can not tell, just give your best guess.", "When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong> to hear the first sound beep."], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "To begin, please use the same volume as in the previous task.<p> Click <strong>Continue</strong> to proceed.</p>", "choices": ["Continue"]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Is the right headphone in your right ear, and the left headphone in your left ear? It is very important!", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_2_zPtZsVZSQCNGIkWk.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_2_k4I1GQvpy4ilMYgN.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_1_tqkZcBQEluMBVhD9.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_2_5lniKIENeiKJc7pr.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_2_F0dYY561mDAJ0yBJ.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_2_0oZeuxhm32T7FE99.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_2_8IteTZ1LuZ01E45c.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_2_DuGtavvW679cTfBe.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_1_JqouHecwdwq2fKrW.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_2_fshrDEJKcJHJjHVd.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_1_UqgZkZpsVhvataj1.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_2_NERvZEsloHYSBef6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_2_RgZbwLHaGWSueJkb.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_2_ib0Ya82IuLhwjx4Q.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_1_VNpw2RODZsM84A4K.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_2_MvWHEvNu3oE9fwiL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_1_CR8eNO7GQgH6U8aL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_1_IkiyRLbj5ksN2ewe.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_2_E9ykvcaXpeL04dmK.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_1_A1LlEkU5AMLeuPOJ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_1_vBZ57N6SyELVYhcm.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_2_6fJWSK7SkWSYuJb4.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_1_s22ZZ1Gf4PQtPcR7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_1_sxP37estiExm4Biz.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_1_rTpYh6vSf7y7Ka1S.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_1_3axZgqrM5PT9qNak.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_2_Zdrs5GPn9bF1DSKy.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_1_BUDYjaaC24xigwni.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_1_xXgg9IebNDYPna3Q.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_2_KipRYa7Bcuxg9nv7.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_2_0cghiZZk2EerhzOR.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_2_vPIlExOfkTB9A4Af.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_2_NYkMjCdKtrmm07kU.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_2_ptNOypyN03mnwqtn.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/3.2dB_1_9TJ7cCL53OHEWGOd.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ILD": "3.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_1_MOHYBfMsA0A5c1YQ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_1_PlTkm9g06pKphxfR.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_1_JTD1ljEmJiEFxmwo.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_1_yAmxLPmr16pgtyYc.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_1_nn0Rwu5jF3X1JHyS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_1_7hdSlErVdZxdhcIT.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.1dB_2_SZLNBvdanDYe9ALF.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.1dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.2dB_2_tH30sVtIGNgvNfbE.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.2dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/1.6dB_2_w7TraWJacqNB7tjv.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "1.6dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_2_wYRZ3q8KBpsYThl9.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.8dB_1_JWFfLa5qOux1RpOd.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.8dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_1_6exjOW35WN8fGk2V.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ILD/main/0.4dB_2_T8aCtGIaYIyVarOl.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ILD": "0.4dB"}}]}